<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
 <channel>
  <title>
   all events
  </title>
  <link>
   https://etsy.com/
  </link>
  <description>
   New in etsy
  </description>
  <language>
   en
  </language>
  <lastBuildDate>
   Mon, 04 Feb 2019 06:56:20 -0000
  </lastBuildDate>
  <item>
   <title>
    Frame Thing Quote CAT IN THE Hat svg file digital file instant download quote thing 1 thing 2 008
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/663902548/frame-thing-quote-cat-in-the-hat-svg?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    ·······················THANKS FOR VISIT MY SHOP··························· 



***Digital Download***  *****Instant Downoad***** 

This means you will get a digital file printable, nothing physycal will be shipped to you. 


DESCRIPTION: 


Product: &amp;quot;FRAME THING&amp;quot; digital file  


You will receive a folder in zip format  


The color shown in the images are merely demonstrative, the files you 

will receive can be modified by you so you can choice your favorite 

color. 


Download includes SVG, DXF, EPS, JPG AND PNG files in a zipped 

folder. 


How it Works? 


After your payment, etsy will send you an email with a link to your 

downloadable files. This will be sent to the email that is registered with 

your etsy account. You should receive an email within a few minutes. If not 

you must check your spam folder. 

Also the files will be in your purchase history. 


How do i unzip the files? 


*If you have a Windows computer follow the next steps: 

1right click on file 

2select Extract All 

3select the location you would like the file to be placed 

4select OK 

5the file is now unzipped and ready to use. 


*If you have Mac computer: 

just double click on the zipped folder 


About files compatibility: 


SVG is compatible with: 

Silhouette Designer Edition, Make the cut (MTC), Sure cuts a lot (SCAL), Brother 

Scan and Cut &amp;quot;Canvas&amp;quot; and Cricut Design Space. 

DXF is compatible with: 

Silhouette Studio Basic Edition 

EPS is compatible with: 

Adobe Illustrator, Corel Draw, and Inkscape. 

PLEASE CONFIRM YOUR COMPATIBILITY WITH YOUR MACHINES OR PROGRAMS 


I want to offer a good customer service so please do not hesitate to make 

questions about ítems, i will try to reply during bussiness hours. 


[[[[[[[[[[  IMPORTANT INFO]]]]]]]]] 


*You can’t share or resell these files in digital format, anyway you can 

use them to make physical products and sell them. 


*Prior to your purchase please make sure that your software and 

machine can work with the offered files. 

*Due to the nature of the digital file i can not offer any refunds. 


*These files can be used for decorations, vinyls, shirts, mugs, onesies, 

stickers, etc. 



Thanks for visit!!·
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Black Leather Mask Pirate Lone Ranger Domino Simple Small Masquerade Don Juan Robin Batman Carnival Mardi gras Halloween Cosplay Cat Burglar
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/151467416/black-leather-mask-pirate-lone-ranger?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    Leather Mask. If you need this mask in another color, feel free to contact us.

Features:
• 100% Genuine Leather: Durable + Flexible + Lightweight
• Painted with quality acrylic paints.
• Double strand of adjustable elastic so you can adjust the strap length to your head size.

Artwork and images are copyrighted © LME Masks
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    10 PIECES - 1&amp;quot; - SOLID Zinc Metal O Rings - Nickel Plate Finish
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/175244517/10-pieces-1-solid-zinc-metal-o-rings?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    10 PIECES - 1&amp;quot; SOLID Zinc Metal O Rings - Nickel Plate Finish

SOLID, NOT SPLIT, NO SEAMS
----------------------------
NEED MORE? here&amp;#39;s a listing for 100
https://www.etsy.com/listing/175244703/100-pieces-1-solid-zinc-metal-o-rings?ref=shop_home_active_1&amp;ga_search_query=1%2Bzinc%2Bo%2B100
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Love My Cat Unique Coffee Mug
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/564659935/love-my-cat-unique-coffee-mug?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    Get this Love My Cat Unique Coffee Mug from TikiGear.

Love cats? Great gift for cat lovers everywhere.

• Ceramic
• Dishwasher and microwave safe
• White and glossy
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Dog collar slides. Dog collar bow tie. Cat collar slides. Cat collar bow tie. Pet collar slides. Pet bows. Cupcakes and flowers collar slide
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/666477112/dog-collar-slides-dog-collar-bow-tie-cat?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    Dog or cat collar slide. Fabric bow tie with elastic on back to decorate your pet&amp;#39;s collar!

White with cupcakes and flowers print bow tie. 
Black or white elastic on back. 

I line the bows so they are firm and more durable, please send me a convo if you prefer unlined bows, just the top fabric so it is soft  and manageable.
If I do not receive a convo with instructions you will receive a lined bow tie.

The option of &amp;quot;elastic to fit&amp;quot; is where you choose the width of the collar your pet will wear with this bow tie.

***Listing is for bow tie slide only, not collar.

Please let me know if you have any questions. I am glad to help!
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Dog collar / tribal dog collar / puppy collar / dog gift / ethnic dog collar / bohemian dog collar / aztec dog collar / black dog collar
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/666477060/dog-collar-tribal-dog-collar-puppy?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    Bright, colorful and authentic handmade dog collar size S. 
Each design is unique and made with a lot of love and dedication! 

*Size S*
-11&amp;quot;- 15&amp;quot;
- Adjustable, 4 holes.

*Please make sure you MEASURE YOUR DOG&amp;#39;S NECK before choosing a size*

*General Measurements*
-Length with buckle: 15.5&amp;quot;
-Length without buckle: 15&amp;quot;
-Width: 0.75&amp;quot;

*Please convo me if you need any additional information.
*We also do wholesale.

Please allow 1-2 business days for processing.
The item you see in the picture is the item you will receive, although I have to warn you sometimes pictures don&amp;#39;t make justice to such beautiful colors! :)

Please contact if you need a particular type of shipment.
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Fine Art Print of Original Watercolor Painting - The Heron &amp; The Hummingbird
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/588681467/fine-art-print-of-original-watercolor?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    This is an archival art print of my original &amp;#39;The Heron &amp; The Hummingbird&amp;#39; illustration.

It is printed with archival pigment inks on professional heavyweight fine art paper.

Paper size: 8 x 10 inches, 20.3 x 25.4 cm
Image size: 7.75 x 9.75 inches, 19.69 x 24.77 cm

There is a thin white border around the image, making it suitable for easy framing in a standard 8 x 10 inch frame or in a larger frame with a mat that has a standard 8 x 10 inch opening.

Ships in a protective archival sleeve in a rigid envelope.

*Please note that Washington state residents will incur a 9.5% sales tax.*


To return to my shop: https://maggierutherford.etsy.com

To find out more about my work: http://maggierutherford.com
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Digital file includes with files. Formats: 2 svg , 2 png , 2 eps , 2 dxf , 2 jpg
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/663046144/digital-file-includes-with-files-formats?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    Commercial use ok!

BUY 2 GET 1 on digital files using the coupon code: FREE1
BUY 3 GET 2 on digital files using the coupon code: FREE2
BUY 5 GET 3 on digital files using the coupon code: FREE3


This is a DIGITAL item for INSTANT DOWNLOAD! No PHYSICAL ITEM will be mailed!
Use for Silhouette, Cricut and other cutting machines.

Download contains 1 zip files
3 SVG
3 DXF
3 EPS 
3 JPG 
3 PNG

THIS IS NOT A FINISHED PRODUCT.

Commercial use ok!
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Not all who wander are lost Custom Pet ID Tag circle, Personalized Dog Tag, Identification name tag, Cat Tag, Anodized, Bag Tag
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/561649642/not-all-who-wander-are-lost-custom-pet?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    Not all who wander are lost Pet ID Tag. Don&amp;#39;t let your pet out without one! 

Available in Black, Red, Green, Blue, Lt. Blue, Purple, Hot Pink, Pink, Silver, Gold, Orange

These can also be used as a cat ID tag, lunch box tag, bag tag, identification name tag and more!

PRODUCT FEATURES
- Glossy finish, circle tag
- High quality anodized aluminum metal
- UV Resistant and Waterproof. Cleans up easily with a towel.
- Split ring included.
- Double-Sided (Add your pet&amp;#39;s name / your number to the back.)
- Tag Size is 1.25&amp;quot; x 1&amp;quot;

HOW TO ORDER
When you check out, please include this information (in the &amp;quot;Message to Seller&amp;quot; box):
1. Pet Name and Number


OPTIONAL ADD-ONs
Add a silencer to your purchase of this ID tag! They are clear, silicone bands that glow in the dark. They do a great job at protecting the tag from wear and tear, and help reduce noise.


Please note:
Color may be slightly different than what you are seeing on your screen.

All collars and ID tags are not indestructible. Sometimes things can happen that can damage your item. Please be aware, If your pet scratches at the collar, it can damage the top layer. Over time, the printed surface of the ID tags will become scratched / chipped from hitting things like the hardware on the collar. The ID tags are durable, but they are not chew resistant.

--CUSTOM DESIGNS --
Custom items are available. Message me with any questions you may have.
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Cat Mama - Bella + Canvas Unisex Tee, Cat Mama Tee, Cat mom shirt, dog mom, cat mom, pet parent shirt, dog mom tee, fur mom tee, fur mama
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/500553616/cat-mama-bella-canvas-unisex-tee-cat?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    ★PLEASE READ ORDERING INSTRUCTIONS BEFORE PURCHASING★

Cat Mama - Bella + Canvas Unisex Tee, Cat Mama Tee, Cat mom shirt, dog mom, cat mom, pet parent shirt, dog mom tee, fur mom tee, fur mama

The main picture in this listing is Deep Heather Unisex Tee

Click the link below for other available styles

https://www.etsy.com/listing/480406014/cat-mama-bella-canvas-slouchy-and?ga_search_query=fur+mama&amp;ref=shop_items_search_3

If you would like this design if in a different style, no problem! Just send me a message and I will make a custom listing for you.

Our shirts and tanks are made with high quality Siser heat transfer vinyl or glitter and pressed using a professional heat press in our home studio.

Description: - Unisex Tee
• 4.2 oz., 100% combed and ring-spun cotton (unless otherwise noted)
• 30 single
• Retail fit
• Unisex sizing
• Shoulder taping
• Side-seamed

Athletic Heather:
• 90% combed and ring-spun cotton/10% poly.

Other Heather colors:
• 52% combed and ring-spun cotton/48% poly.

Marble colors:
• 91% poly/9% combed and ring-spun cotton
• 4.0 oz.



★ORDERING INSTRUCTIONS:★

Choose your size/style and color from the drop down on the top right

Leave a note in the &amp;quot;notes&amp;quot; section with your choice of color for the text. Options are listed below:

Smooth Font Options:
White
Black
Gold
Silver
Pink
Light Pink
Purple
Red
Green
Yellow
Orange
Navy Blue
Royal Blue
Pale Blue
Fluorescent Pink
Fluorescent Yellow
Fluorescent Coral

Glitter Font Options:
White Glitter
Black Glitter
Black Silver Glitter
Silver Glitter
Gold Glitter
Blue Glitter
Light Green Glitter
Aqua Glitter
Purple Glitter
Red Glitter
Hot Pink Glitter
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    CATS Classic &amp; Modern Musical Theater Poster Print - Satin Paper - A4 A3 A2 - Home Wall Decor
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/675686257/cats-classic-modern-musical-theater?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    CATS - music theatre poster print.
Our prints are made to order using top quality durable UV and fade resistant inks, printed on 240gsm SATIN photo paper. Delivered unframed.

AVAILABLE SIZES:
A6 sample  - 105 x 148mm (no watermark)
A4  - 210 x 297mm
A3  - 297 x 420mm
A2  - 420 x 594mm

FREE UK postage, fast processing time, typically delivered within 1-3 days from purchase.
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Sets of Small Solid Wool Cat Toys - Hand-felted colorful wool ball toys for small pets, adult cats, kittens, ferrets, hamster, gerbils
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/291511085/sets-of-small-solid-wool-cat-toys-hand?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    Sets of hand-felted, solid wool pet toys - size small. Great for cats, kittens and small pets. Each of the balls is about 2 cm / 1 inch in diameter, though they may vary a small amount because they are hand felted.

Sold in 40+ color options, please see the second photo for the names of the colors. I&amp;#39;m happy to send you any combination of the colors shown for your set of 6, 12, 18, 24. I am also happy to do a custom quantity if those aren&amp;#39;t what you are looking for. 

I also carry a larger size wool cat toy in my shop well suited for adult cats. Check out this link for all the options: https://www.etsy.com/shop/redheadandbluellc?ref=hdr_shop_menu&amp;section_id=22158608

Want to really boost your kitty&amp;#39;s play? Buy my catnip oil kit and watch your cat become a kitten again! Here&amp;#39;s the link: https://www.etsy.com/listing/110341383/re-scent-me-kit-for-cat-toys-can-scent?ref=shop_home_active_6

Use code COMBO when ordering more than one item in my shop, you will receive 5% off! Want a larger discount? Sign up for RH&amp;B VIP List and receive an instant 10% coupon for your first order (with monthly coupons to follow!). Sign up here: http://eepurl.com/cx2Md5
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Lucy-Fur Kitty Necklaces
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/680317993/lucy-fur-kitty-necklaces?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    These measure approximately 20” in length, made with lobster clasp closures. Large cameos are 30x40mm excluding ornate frame, smaller kitty cameos are 18X25mm.
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Custom Pet Portrait- STRING ART!
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/666473730/custom-pet-portrait-string-art?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    You send me your pets picture and I’ll do my best to recreate your fur babies into a string art portrait!

Reclaimed and recycled wood that has been sanded and turned into a one of a kind work.

Any size available!

Any colors combination!

Custom orders can be made.
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Black Cat With Big Eyes  Design files svg studio3 pdf jpeg cut File Print And Cutout Svg Pdf Studio 3 Jpeg Four Cricut Babyshower Birthday
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/597941519/black-cat-with-big-eyes-design-files-svg?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    This is a cut or print image file that can be used in a variation of ways and with a lot of different materials.

You are able to cut using paper, vinyl and many other cutter friendly materials.

You can either print and cut or just print the image and use it on iron-on crafting projects that use a heat press or iron such as clothing, bags, pillow cases or DIY crafting such as making a pillow with this image as a iron-on.

Excellent a just a stand alone print out for cards, invitations ect the possibilities are limitless. 

This design is formatted to work with Silhouette Studio (Basic, Designer, and Business Editions), Cricut Design Space, &amp; Brother ScanNCutCanvas.

***Important***

Cricut Design Space does NOT support uploading SVG&amp;#39;S from mobile devices such as ipad &amp; iPhone ect as of this time.
The design files must be uploaded first to Cricut Design Space from a computer then are able to be accessed from your Mobil device ipad, iPhone ect from the app.

This listing includes 5 files:

1 SVG Cut File 
1 Studio3 Cut File
1 Studio2 Cut File
1 PDF
1 JPEG

Please: No reselling the files. 

The zip file containing the cut file/s will be instantly available to download after payment is confirmed. No physical item will be shipped.

Here&amp;#39;s how to download file after purchase: https://www.etsy.com/help/article/3949

Digital Download Listings are non-refundable. If you have difficultly downloading the file, please message me your email address and I&amp;#39;ll be happy to email the file to you.  

Browse my main shop page for similar items here:
https://www.etsy.com/shop/PandapawsStudio?ref=seller-platform-mcnav
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Kool Kitty Gymnastics Grip Bag - Personalized
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/627744662/kool-kitty-gymnastics-grip-bag?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    *** Please note, Custom orders are no longer guaranteed to deliver by Christmas *** 

This Kool Kitty grip bag is perfect for carrying all your accessories to gym or dance class.  It is a perfect size at 9&amp;quot;x10&amp;quot;.  Comes with a cord lock to make sure all your items are closed in tight. You can also have your gymnast name put on this bag (please email us with the name you would like to add name).

 *   A great polyester lycra bag in a mix of blues. Sublimated with a Kool Kitty on the front
   
 *  Bag is 9&amp;quot; x 10&amp;quot;
    
 * Perfect for holding your grips, wristbands, tape, etc.
   
 * Font may be smaller on longer names (max of 9 letters for name) Please note customized items are not returnable.


We also sell the matching leotard!!  See our store for more products!

Please note, sublimated items are made as ordered, and may take up to 2 weeks before they leave our warehouse, regardless of shipping method. If you are needing it to ship sooner than this, please email us and we can check our stock to see if we have one ready for immediate shipping. 


If you have any questions, please feel free to email us or contact us.

Snowflake Designs
1-888-509-6234
Monday - Thursday 9:30 - 5:30
Fridays 9:30 - 5:00
Closed on weekends
Pacific Time
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Small Cat Tags - Pet ID - Dog Tag - Pet Accessories - Collar Tag - Pets - Pet Tag - Metal ID - Custom ID Tag - Personalized Pet Tag - Moon
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/495733213/small-cat-tags-pet-id-dog-tag-pet?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    Personalized Pet ID Tag - Includes pet&amp;#39;s name and a phone number.

● 7/8&amp;quot; in diameter
● 18 Guage thickness
● Rustic Copper dipped
● Pet&amp;#39;s name replaces the name displayed, phone number is stamped on the back.
● Split rings included 

I ship worldwide and provide free combined shipping for multiple orders.
Thanks for checking out my designs.
Dan - TagemDesigns
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Cat Quote Decorative Pillow Cat Thoughts Cat Sayings Pet Decor Cat Pillow Cover
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/562833570/cat-quote-decorative-pillow-cat-thoughts?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    This is a stylish whimsical cat sayings (thoughts) on a 16x16 Handmade pillow cover. This will make a great gift for your cat lover friend or for yourself. These thoughts are representative of the sassy independent felines that we know so well. 

Type: Cover

Size: 16&amp;quot; x 16&amp;quot;

Fill Material: Polyester Fiber

Fabric: 100% Cotton

Would recommend hand washing or gentle cycle.

Thank you for stopping by
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    RETRO CANDY DISH • Mid Century Modern Mcm Nut Tray Condiment Serving Atomic Space Age Kitsch 60s Mad Men Home Decor Luxury Pet Cat Food
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/666476422/retro-candy-dish-mid-century-modern-mcm?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    Vintage mid-century modern serving tray. Leave out your favorite nuts and candies, like grandma used to. Use it as a catchall for your keys &amp; wallet at the entryway. Use it as a luxury pet cat food dish. This kitschy stainless steel platter makes the perfect accent for 60s Mad Men style interior decoration. The back is stamped, &amp;quot;International Decorator Stainless 18-8.&amp;quot;

• • • • • • • • • • • • • • • 

CONDITION:
Excellent vintage condition.

• • • • • • • • • • • • • • • 

DIMENSIONS:
13.5 x 6 x 1.5 inches

• • • • • • • • • • • • • • • 

SEE MORE FROM MY SHOP:
godo.etsy.com
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Country Spirits Spooky Tree Halloween Cross Stitch Pattern by Homespun Elegance
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/666476360/country-spirits-spooky-tree-halloween?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    Country Spirits Spooky Tree Halloween Cross Stitch Pattern by Homespun Elegance. Excellent used condition. Smoke free home.
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Cats on Sites 2018
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/657405621/cats-on-sites-2018?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    Priority Shipping Included!

A4A member, Katie Hoffman, designed this fun calendar to highlight archaeological sites in a playful way by adding cats. 

It is great for Cat Lovers, Archaeologists, White Elephant Gift Exchanges, or just for fun.

8.5X11 inches

Art4Archaeology is an artist collective with dedicated members who are passionate about preservation of prehistoric and historic cultural resources.

All proceeds from this sale will be provided to Nevadans for Cultural Preservation (NVFCP), a 501c3 nonprofit with a mission to preserve cultural resources (archaeology) through education. To learn more visit www.nvfcp.org

If you are able to pick this item up in Las Vegas, NV, please contact rayette@nvfcp.org for a $5.00 coupon code .
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Castor Collar, Custom Dog Collar, Cat Collar, Moon Collar, Metallic Collar, Space Collar, Dog on the Moon
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/676655465/castor-collar-custom-dog-collar-cat?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    This Iisting is for the Castor collar 

Dog on the Moon collars are hand-crafted by yours truly here in the United States. Each collar is custom made to order for your totally out of this world pet! Dog on the Moon gear is created with individual attention to detail, lots of love, and a surplus positive vibes. Each collar is made with a durable and waterproof webbing core surrounded by multiple layers of cotton fabric. Our recycled packaging is hand-stamped and each collar purchase comes with a free gift. Please read the full listing description and see all example photos.

Available collar widths: 
3/4 inch (2 cm), 1 inch (2.5 cm), 1.5 inch (3.8 cm), 2 inch (5 cm)

Available collar styles: 
Slip on, buckle, martingale, martingale chain, cat collar

Available collar hardware:
Silver, brass, black

———————————————————
3/4 inch width- This one is for the little guys! Cats and small pets under 20 lbs.

1 inch width- Comfortably fits pets of almost any size, from corgis to labradors!

1.5 inch width- One size up from our 1 inch width, this is the most loved size among medium- large pets and those with a little extra collar consuming fluff! This is the width I personally prefer for my adult male Siberian Husky.

2 inch width- The eye catcher. this width is for pets with a larger than life size to match their personality! A great option for German Shepherds, Giant breeds, Malamutes, dogs with extra long necks, and long haired large pets.

———————————————————
Slip on- This unique collar features a sleek design that really shows off the print, it is a customer favorite. This buckle-less collar does NOT function as a martingale and tighten when pulled. Made with plenty of adjusting room, you can be assured the collar will be able to go over your pet’s head and also be tightened snug on their neck. Available in silver, brass (gold), and black hardware.

Buckle- The standard in the collar world, this classic design features a slide release style buckle. Available in black plastic buckle, silver metal buckle &amp; hardware, and brass (gold) metal buckle &amp; hardware.  Silver hardware comes standard with the black plastic buckle.

Martingale- This collar design consists of two main loops. When tension is applied this collar tightens and prevents the dog from backing out of the collar. I recommend researching this collar type before purchasing. Available in silver, brass (gold), and black hardware. 

Martingale Chain- This collar functions the same way mentioned above but the second loop is a silver metal half check-chain instead of a fabric loop.

Cat Collar- Our cat collars have a wide range of length that adjusts from 7”-13” and fit almost any feline neck measurement. They are outfitted with a super lightweight break-away style buckle, silver adjuster slide, and an extra small silver metal D-ring to attach a bell or ID tag. Every cat collar comes with a jingle bell. 

———————————————————
Collar Length: All dog collars are made with 2-3 inches of adjusting room in each direction from the neck measurement specified in the drop down menu. For example: a collar length of 16 inches is selected from the drop down menu, this collar will have an estimated adjustable range of 13-19 inches. If you have a growing puppy and would prefer extra wiggle room, write your specifications in the notes to seller upon checkout and I will do my best to meet your request. Please provide puppy’s current neck measurement and estimated adult size. 

Our cat collars are one size fits all and have an adjustable length of 7- 13 inches. When purchasing a cat collar please select the 7 inches collar length from the drop down menu. Custom sizing available per request before purchasing.

How to measure your pet’s neck: Use a fabric tape measure and measure around your pet&amp;#39;s neck where a collar would normally sit. Pulling it snug, you should be able to fit 2 fingers between the neck and tape measure. This number (in inches) is your collar length. I recommend measuring twice to ensure accurate sizing. If you have any questions do not hesitate to send me a message, Dog on the Moon is not responsible for any customer error including inaccurate sizing.

Centimeter to Inch Conversion: 2.5 cm = 1 in

———————————————————
All items ordered under this listing will be made using the same fabric that is pictured; however, the orientation and isolation of the fabric will be different, making each collar unique! Please acknowledge that I do not produce these fabrics myself and colors may appear slightly different in person compared to photos on a screen.
———————————————————
Care Information: I recommend hand washing your collar. Using warm water and mild detergent, gently scrub the entirety of the fabric loop and rinse thoroughly. These collars are designed with a waterproof core so you do not have to worry about moisture build up (or the smell that can accompany it). Remove excess water by patting with a towel, drying the hardware thoroughly. Lay collar on a flat surface to dry. Do not place in a commercial dryer. Once completely dry, your collar is as good as new! Wrinkles can be easily combatted with a quick pass of an iron on the LOWEST setting. With proper care and maintenance, your collar will last through all of your most memorable adventures and well deserved naps! 
———————————————————
Processing and Shipping: Our current processing time is 2-3 weeks. Thank you for your patience, I work my hardest to get your items out to you as soon as possible!  Average delivery time (after you receive your shipping confirmation) is 2-4 business days for orders within the United States and 7-14 business days everywhere else. Dog on the Moon is not responsible for any customs fees or shipping delays. I am not responsible if your package is lost or stolen during transport. I am not responsible for any customer error when providing an accurate shipping address. If you have never purchased an item from the United States, I recommend looking into your local customs regulations at your nearest post office.
———————————————————
Treats: All domestic orders come with a single ingredient treat for your pet, read your shipping confirmation email thoroughly for more information on your treat. Please acknowledge any dietary restrictions your pet may have before feeding.
———————————————————
Crystals: Every collar purchase comes with a crystal or stone; charged with positive energy and ready to join you on your journey! I am very passionate about crystals and the metaphysical side of life, as a Reiki master I feel that it is really my duty to help spread the pure loving energy of the Earth to anyone and everyone possible! I hope you enjoy this free gift.
———————————————————
Custom Orders: If you have a clear vision of a design or pattern that you do not see available in the shop, send me a message and I will do my best to meet your custom collar requests. If you would like a unique mix of hardware or need a collar length that is not available in the drop down menu, send me a message before purchasing. If you would like a specific thread color used on your collar, leave your request in the notes to seller at checkout. 
———————————————————
I do not recommend leaving a collar on your pet unsupervised. Keep your best friend safe; remove all accessories before leaving your pet alone to avoid choking and strangulation hazards. Dog on the Moon is not responsible for any injuries caused by misuse or negligence. Dog on the Moon is not responsible if your pet chews, rips, or reduces the product value in any way. Please do not request an exchange or refund if Fido gets too frisky and a collar is mistaken for a chew toy, dogs will be dogs after all!
———————————————————
Dog on the Moon is very active on Instagram, follow our page @dogonthemoon for exclusive discounts, sales, and contests. I love staying connected with customers; let me know your pet’s Instagram page in the notes to seller upon checkout! Tag @dogonthemoon and use hashtag #dogonthemoon in your photos so the world can see your pet!

-
-
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    BOBCAT Large REAL BONE Skull
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/666476186/bobcat-large-real-bone-skull?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    BOBCAT- Real Bone-LARGE Skull
Professionally cleaned and disinfected, but unbleached, bone  is left in its natural color.
Prime specimen from the Ozark mountains. 
LARGE CAT Skull measures approximately 4 5/8 inches long, around 3 1/8 inches wide,
And about 2 1/2 inches tall.
VERY NICE SKULL!
1 available, buyer will receive the exact skull pictured above.
NO TEETH MISSING!    #1 QUALITY!
Incredible addition to your collection, display, or next craft project.
............................................................................................................................................................................................................................................

All items we offer for sale are legally taken and can legally be sold by us according to the laws of the State of Arkansas.Ozark Artistry assumes when you order an item that you can legally possess that item according to the laws of your state or country. If you order items from us and you cannot possess them according to the laws of your state or country, Ozark Artistry will hold you responsible for any penalties and/or legal fees incurred by Ozark Artistry.
All offerings of merchandise shall be interpreted to mean that Ozark Artistry is not offering to sell items of which the sale is prohibited in your state.

Because we carry many one-of-a-kind items, all items are sold on an availability basis only.

We are not responsible for typographical or clerical errors on this web site. 

ALL SALES ARE FINAL.
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Dog collar slides. Dog collar bow tie. Cat collar slides. Cat collar bow tie. Pet collar slides. Pet bows. Brown with vines collar slide
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/666476172/dog-collar-slides-dog-collar-bow-tie-cat?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    Dog or cat collar slide. Fabric bow tie with elastic on back to decorate your pet&amp;#39;s collar!

Multi brown vines bow tie. 
Black or white elastic on back. 

I line the bows so they are firm and more durable, please send me a convo if you prefer unlined bows, just the top fabric so it is soft  and manageable.
If I do not receive a convo with instructions you will receive a lined bow tie.

The option of &amp;quot;elastic to fit&amp;quot; is where you choose the width of the collar your pet will wear with this bow tie.

***Listing is for bow tie slide only, not collar.

Please let me know if you have any questions. I am glad to help!
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
  <item>
   <title>
    Meow Clip Art | Hand Drawn Cat Girl Fashion Illustration Jewels Masquerade Graphics | Planner Stickers, Planner Girl | Digital Cliparts
   </title>
   <link>
    https://www.etsy.com/listing/548521983/meow-clip-art-hand-drawn-cat-girl?utm_source=createrss&amp;utm_medium=api&amp;utm_campaign=api
   </link>
   <description>
    A glamorous, bold yet feminine digital artwork collection featuring a sexy lady in a feline couture costume / outfit. Matching fashion illustrations include cats, jewels, gemstones, glitter kisses, sexy boots, delicate mask, gold and glitter confetti.

You will receive 19 individual graphics to create your own design arrangement and layout. The artwork is original and hand drawn by me.

The clip art set is perfect for planner stickers, planner dashboard, planner inserts, scrap booking, website, fashion boutique, branding, fashion blog, party decor, photography marketing, hen&amp;#39;s night, bachelorette party etc

Matching digital papers:

https://www.etsy.com/au/listing/548524503

♥&amp;lt;♥&amp;lt;♥ WHAT YOU WILL RECEIVE ♥&amp;gt;♥&amp;gt;♥&amp;gt;

♥ 19 high quality images with transparent background
♥ All clips combined will fit a 25 x 20 Inches Paper - individual image sizes vary with girl  3.1 x 15 Inches, a black cat 3.8 x 5.4 Inches
♥ PNG File format at 300 dpi

Note: This is a digital file available as an instant download, no physical item will be sent.

&amp;lt;♥&amp;lt;♥&amp;lt;♥ Terms of Use ♥&amp;gt;♥&amp;gt;♥&amp;gt;

The clip art graphics are strictly for your personal use (whether for your hobby or business) and not for profit.
You may not resell, share or claim any part of the designs as your own.

If you are interested in using them to create items to sell, you are required to purchase a commercial license available here:
https://www.etsy.com/au/listing/240310974/basic-commercial-license-for-commercial

I do check uses from time to time to prevent abuse and to keep the designs premium. Please contact me if in doubt :)

By purchasing this file you agree to the Terms of Use and Bloomsical Shop&amp;#39;s Policies:
https://www.etsy.com/au/shop/Bloomsical/policy


© 2017 Bloomsical. All rights reserved. You may not re-sell, share or copy my designs.
   </description>
   <guid isPermaLink="false">
    no
   </guid>
  </item>
 </channel>
</rss>